A Finding Aid to the Douglas Leigh Papers, 1903-1999, in the Archives of American Art
Archives of American Art
- Urban Improvement Project Files, 1903-1992; Series 13; Archival Resource Key; (Box 9, 14, 28-32, OV 34; 2.2 linear feet)
  - Grand Central Station Project Oversized Drawings and Blueprints, 1946-1965; Archival Resource Key (Oversize 34)